tutorviacomputer.com 2017-05-11

# Privacy Policy

We believe that your privacy is very important. We understand that you are trusting us to act in a responsible manner when you provide us with personal information. Your trust is very important to us. The information you provide will only be used to help us provide you with better service. We never provide any of your personal information to other companies or individuals.

## What personal information do you collect?

When you visit our Web site and access information you remain anonymous. The only personal information we have is the information your choose to provide us.

## What statistical information do you collect?

We collect the following statistical information: IP address, accesses, and referring URL.

## Do you use cookies and/or Web beacons?

We use a very popular software package to build this site. It uses cookies and perhaps Web beacons. We so not access those cookies or Web beacons. We work with third parties that serve ads to our site. Some of these agencies may use cookies and/or Web beacons to collect information, in the course of serving ads. You can set your browser to prevent the installation of cookies.  
These companies may also use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,[click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).
